What do you want to do?
Who are you?
Me? I'm the owner of this house.
That's the destiny.
I never sold this place.
Get out.
I don't want to stay here.
I want you out by the end of this week.
If not, you'll be gone with this building.
No way, this is my house.
You have no right to do that.
Why do you keep torturing me and following me around?
Who are you? Why are you doing this to me?
What a bad person you are to treat me like this.
How can you do this to me?
Do you think what you did was okay?
How did it feel when you walked away from a dying person?
What I've done
is nothing.
Compared to what you took away from me.
Don't show up in front of me
by the end of this week.
Are you done crying?
You think I'm pathetic, don't you?
A little bit.
It would be better if he listened to your song till the end.
This is what I think.
Don't cry for someone who won't cry for you.
Wipe away your tears.
Why don't you cry for someone who'll cry for you?
What should I do with the house?
Just leave it.
Stop stalking Kang Yoo Jung now.
Yes, sir!
So annoyed.
Was that you?
You can't just hit people and run away.
Because of you.
How dare you hurt what's mine?
Don't look at me with innocent eyes.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why do you have to torture me like this?
Just stay in jail.
When you get out, I'll make your life miserable.
Yoo Jung!
Do Hoon!
What's going on?
Nothing! It's okay.
Let me see. Are you hurt?
We have to move out.
The landlord came.
He wants us out by the end of the week.
This is so sudden. Let me talk to him.
Don't.
I'll take care of it. Don't worry.
But...
He won't listen to you.
I'll talk to him. Let me deal with him.
I do owe him money.
What are you doing here?
I don't know what I'm doing here.
Aren't you going home?
Home? I have nothing to do there.
Did something happen?
Something?
Is it about you singing in public?
You've had stage fright since you were little.
Who did you want to impress?
You don't normally sing on stage for no reason.
Jo Min Hyuk! I didn't sing for anyone else.
I did it for you.
Was that your present for me?
You already have everything,
I can do nothing but sing for you.
Why didn't you tell me earlier? I happened to...
I'm off. I'm getting tired.
Se Yeon!
Can't you sing now?
You want me to listen, right?
Min Hyuk.
Do you think you can cry for me?
Can you cry for me?
What is this? It's so unlike you.
I'm done.
What?
This marriage.
How did it feel when you walked away from a dying person?
This building?
This is nothing.
Compared to what you took away from me.
Dad, we have to go.
Let's go traveling.
Let's go to see the sea and mountains.
Sea.
Let's go on a trip.
Good. Sea.
Let's go.
Take this off. It's itchy.
No. You have to wear it all the time.
Take it off. Please take it off.
Dad! Dad!
Forty-five, forty-six, forty-seven.
When I was your age, I had no fat around my belly.
I was so fit.
Mom!
Five more!
You're not born with a perfect body.
It depends on how much effort you put into it.
If I had your genes,
I wouldn't have to do this.
Why do I have daddy's genes?
Yes.
I wish you had my genes, too.
I don't look like you at all.
So do my eating habits and fit.
You know what my friends say?
You and I don't look alike at all.
Mom, do you...
What?
Tell me the truth. I'm not a kid anymore.
Did you get plastic surgery?
Absolutely not!
I was born pretty.
Tell me! Where?
Stop!
Tell me! Come on!
Okay! Okay! My eyes!
Where else?
Se Yeon, the other day...
Come on in.
What? Don't you want to cancel the wedding?
This is a business.
This is a good opportunity to cooperate, and this is the prenup. I already signed it.
This is a Lucida Diamond cut in 1999.
It belongs to princeess series.
I don't care about that. What's the most expensive ring?
What about that one?
That one?
What? It's really big.
Give me the biggest or the most expensive ring in the world,
If not, get me the one you'd want me to have.
You don't want to give me anything?
- All the rings are the same. - I'll have that one.
The more I get the better.
Are you going to take penalty if I breach the prenup?
Of course.
It's all written here. Read it carefully.
Whoever violates this contract first will pay.
If I give you the ring, what will you give me?
I can increase your value by marrying you.
Hey, Se Yeon!
Thank you for the ring.
She sure is Shin's daughter.
They only care about themselves.
You know Se Yeon is not like that.
Grow up.
We've been friends since elementary school.
Friends? Stop being silly.
You know who your real friends are when you're in need.
Go over it, make some necessary changes, and send it back.
Yes, sir!
Has Kang Yoo Jung moved out?
I told her to move out by the end of this week.
You told me not to follow her around, so...
But you stil have to know where she is.
I'm sorry.
I've lost my appetite.
You shouldn't have come here.
I know Do Hoon sent you here,
but you shouldn't have come here with your father.
Mother!
Stop! People might misunderstand that.
I'm not your mother. We're not family.
I'm sorry.Mo...
I know I shouldn't have come here,
but my father can't sleep in a strange place.
Dad!
Shoes!
You should have prepared for that.
I told you to pull yourself together.
We only have two rooms.
Do Hoon's going to be late.
Take your father to Do Hoon's room.
Thank you, father.
Stop calling him father.
Thank you.
Dad, it's okay. I'll take care of these complicated problems.
Are you going home?
Yes, I am.
I warned you.
Excuse me?
This is nothing personal. Don't complain about me.
This is an organization, and I'm part of this organization.
I'll see you at the Supreme Prosecutor's Office.
I agreed to go on a date with the manager to get you this job.
Don't mess it up.
Thank you, Hae Ri.
Kwang Soo.
- My shoe's untied. - Yes, sir!
Our boss is really young, right?
What's wrong?
What?
I'm really busy at the moment. Hey! Come quick!
You can work here.
Why did you do that?
Stop! That's enough!
Sorry, I don't think I can work here.
Sorry, Hae Ri. I owe you.
I told her that I don't want to see her, how dare she come to my place?
Hello.
Again?
No. I'm coming now.
Sorry.
She is coming up.
She's coming.
Should I follow her?
No.
I had an early meeting. I'm tired.
Let's go.
Ms.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Dad, what are you doing here?
Yoo Jung, open the door.
It's locked.
This isn't our house anymore.
Let's go.
Open the door.
I'll bring you back here later.
Your mother didn't like dessert at first,
but she came to like the bread that I baked.
She liked my creams buns.
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
His blood vessels are swollen.
We need to do a cerebral artery surgery as soon as possible.
I temporarily treated him with medication.
It's like a time bomb.
Will surgery cure him?
That depends on the recovery condition after the surgery.
Do the surgery, please.
Please save my father.
I won't take it off.
Dad, if you fight like this, you might faint again.
Dad, take it off, please!
No!
Dad. Come on!
If you don't put these on, I'll send you back to the nursing home.
Quickly.
Come on! Hand!
Wow!
Take this as collateral.
Take care of it, I'll come back for it.
I'm Park Hyun Suk, a special prosecutor.
Congressman Kim Chang Suk claimed that he's the victim of a sting operation.
We're going to investigate the truth regarding his claim.
Did you submit your statement to the police?
Yes.
Prosecutor Ahn Do Hoon.
Have you got a minute?
This will be your desk.
These are documents related to Congressman Kim's foreign account.
Why are you giving these to me?
Join the K Corporation Legal Team.
Take it as a signing bonus.
Do I look that simply to you?
I don't think so.
I just feel it's urgent
to cuff Congressman Kim one more time.
Submit your letter of resignation.
Dad!
Doctor.
Mr. Kang Woo Chul!
The third one.
Open your eyes.
Grab his arms.
Please wait outside.
Mr. Kang, open your eyes.
- Wait outside. - Grab his arms.
When can I finish it?
I have to stay up today.
Sir.
If you give me the phone and bank records...
I'm not allowed to give you any work
while you're under investigation.
I guess things aren't going so well.
What are you doing here?
Thank you for your handkerchief.
I don't think you're here just to give this back to me.
It sounds like an excuse.
I don't know why I'm here.
I wanted to talk to someone over a drink,
and you popped into my mind.
I'm busy.
I have lots of cases to take care of...
- I... - Mr. Ahn,
You can go home if you have nothing else to do.
How much can you give me?
How much did you pay?
It was a present.
It's delicate and looks good.
Give me as much as you can.
I'll come back for it.
I'd like to reserve a surgery.
I'll pay the rest later.
Ms. Kang Yoo Jung!
Yes?
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Why do you have the ring
that I bought for my future daughter-in-law?
Do you know how much it's worth?
It's a 150 million KRW ring, and you got 4 million KRW?
Why didn't you just keep it?
It has a serial number, and you can't sell it.
Don't you know that you should give the precious thing back to the owner?
Sorry.
I thought my son gave it to a woman he likes, so I brought you here.
But I don't think that's the case.
Report her to the police.
I gave the ring to her.
Let's go!
Get up!
I told you not to show up again.
How dare you sell my property?
I'll pay you back.
Everyone can say that.
My father's sick and I needed money for his surgery.
I shouldn't have done it.
I guess I lost my mind.
It's your father this time?
You have no shortage of excuses.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Stop saying sorry.
I don't want your apology.
You should suffer as much as I did.
Feel helpless while you lose your loved ones.
You have to realize how painful it is.
Get out!
I'll see you at the police station.
I'm wrong.
Hey, let me go.
Please forgive me this once.
I can't let my father go just like that.
You can take me to the police station.
I'll go to prison. I'll pay for what I did.
Can you wait until I see my father get better
after his surgery?
Please.
If you can let me stay with my father...
Get off of me.
Aren't you ashamed?
Np, I can do worse things than this.
I'm ashamed of what I did to that woman.
I don't think I paid for what I did.
I won't forget it as long as I live.
How can I forget?
Don't mention her.
How dare you mention her?
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
Okay, what are you going to do?
If I save your father,
what can you do for me in return?
As you see, I have lots of money.
I can give you money for your father's surgery.
Se Yeon.
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
I just want to speak ill of someone while drinking.
Who is she?
A woman to see me.
This is my friend, Shin Se Yeon.
And that's Prosecutor Ahn Do Hoon.
How about drinking together?
We'd like to have a drink as well.
Sure. Why not?
Where do you want to go? We have a distinguished guest here.
By the way, I'll wire you the money tomorrow.
Thank you.
If you'll excuse me...
Don't go.
I said don't go.
I did you a favor.
Se Yeon, can I take a rain check?
Are you running away?
You don't like drinking?
You shouldn't run away like that.
I guess it's a little awkward to drink with a stranger.
Have we met before?
I don't think so.
Prosecutor Ahn, I'm a little disappointed.
You always reject my invitations to have a drink.
What do you do?
How do you know Min Hyuk?
A personal friend of mine.
She does everything I ask her to do.
Do Hoon, are you nervous sitting next to a lady?
Why aren't you saying anything?
This is unexpected, and I feel awkward.
I gusee we should introduce some girls to you.
He hasn't been on a date for too long.
What do you think of him?
He's still single. Don't you think he's handsome?
Jo Min Hyuk!
I have a boyfriend.
Really? What does he do?
Something great.
Something great?
Excuse me.
Have you known Min Hyuk for a long time?
Do you know that I'm Min Hyuk's fiance?
No. Please don't misunderstand us.
He... He lent me money for my father's surgery.
That's all.
I shouldn't have come here.
I'm glad you knew that.
I'll go now.
What do you think you're doing?
I didn't do anything.
She came to me and asked me for money for her father's surgery.
What can I do?
Although I hate her, her father is innocent.
I don't just let people die like other people.
Don't you think Kang Yoo Jung is so shameless?
She recognized you, didn't she?
She's sitting next to the person
who put her in jail, yet she didn't flinch.
She paid for what she did.
Don't you think you're being too cruel to her?
I don't know why you're defending her like this.
She's not a criminal anymore.
She's just a citizen who paid for what she did.
What are you talking about?
I don't feel comfortable staying here.
You think you can manipulate people with money.
It makes me sick.
Is she the one who killed Seo Ji Hee?
I'm sorry, it's just...
Min Hyuk! You're not doing this for her.
You just want to arouse others' sympathy so you can do everything you want.
I won't marry you if you keep doing this.
If you think our marriage is business,
try to have a little bit of respect for me.
Excuse me. Have you seen my father?
No.
What do you think you're doing?
How can you beg him for money?
Do you know who he is?
Do Hoon! My father is missing.
He's neither at the hospital nor the bakery.
I didn't find him at the bakery, that's where he goes everytime.
What are you talking about?
My father has disappeared.
Maybe he went to mom's grave.
He sometimes goes there.
I should go there.
Let me go!
Yoo Jung!
My father is missing.
I'll look for him. Calm down.
How can I calm down when my father's missing?
He needs to have surgery. I need to find him.
Report him missing at the police station first.
I'll look for him.
Sir,
please find my father.
He has to do the surgery right away.
I have to find him quickly.
Calm down.
Fill out this form first.
Father.
I don't know where my house is.
Take me to Yoo Jung.
Yes, Yoo Jung's worried about you.
Get in the car.
Thank god!
Drive carefully.
Yes, father.
I mean it.
You hurt Yoo Jung's forehead before.
It rained so heavily that day,
I was worried.
The car was badly damaged.
Thankfully Yoo Jung seemed okay.
You still remember that?
Why not?
You drove that night,
You think I don't know that Yoo Jung is your scrapegoat?
If you do that again,
I won't forgive you.
Do you understand?
Drive safely.
Drive carefully.
Let's call it a day.
Thank you.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
See you tomorrow at 10 a.m.
Prosecutor Ahn Do Hoon.
Are these the principles you talked about?
You said I needed to be flexible
to maintain the principles in this organization.
I didn't know you meant that you would destroy your colleague to get ahead.
Why didn't you tell me that I should forget about principles and truth,
and concentrate on being successful?
You should just tell me that.
Do you think you're clean and just?
That's not true.
I heard how you obtained those files
on Congressman Kim.
Did you go after him
only to reveal the truth?
I don't think so.
You wanted to develop your career
by catching a big fish.
Can you deny that?
Hello.
Yes. Red jacket.
Yes.
Where did you find him?
What? Pohang?
Well...
Thank you for letting the ring incident slide.
Thank you very much.
I'll pay you back even if it takes me my entire life.
I'm in a hurry at the moment.
Sorry.
Please give me a break.
They found my father.
Where is he?
Pohang.
Darn it.
Taxi!
You said Pohang.
Dad. Dad. Dad.
Why?
Oh my god! Dad!
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Please say something.
This is a typical sting operation
by the prosecution.
They were trying to end my career as a politician.
We have found out the truth.
We're going to...
You came straight here.
No one's waiting for me anyway.
I'll go get some tofu.
Stop!
Do you want to advertise that I got out of jail?
That's ridiculous.
Do you think tofu will make me clean?
It's not that bad.
There's someone else crying instead of you.
Have you found an accomodation yet?
Unbelievable!
Are you worried about me?
I can find a place to stay.
If you have nowhere else to go, go find me.
What?
Are you waiting for someone?
I don't like it.
You always smile like that when you're tired.
Take it. It's all I have.
I'll feel a little bit better this way.
I thought a lot in the mourning hall.
When is he coming?
Will he come today? Will he come in the midnight?
I waited and waited, but you never came.
I was thinking, if you came on the 1st day,
I would've relied on you too much,
and I wouldn't have said a proper good-bye to dad.
Yoo Jung.
If you came on the 2nd day, I would've blame you for not coming earlier.
I wouldn't have thought about dad.
Thank you for coming today.
I'm glad that I saw you.
Sorry.
Let's break up.
It's been so hard for both of us, right?
Yoo Jung.
We've tried not to hurt each other, and we just smile.
This isn't right.
Every time you see me, you'll feel guilty,
and you'll try to do something for me.
I'll be uncomfortable looking at you.
It'll repeat.
But I don't regret what I did.
Even if I could do it all over again, I'd do the same thing.
Stop feeling guilty because of that.
What can I do for you?
Let me leave first.
If I leave first, you would remember me for a long time.
I don't think I can watch you walk away.
I can't bear to watch.
I should've bought you good shoes.
I shouldn't take busy as an excuse.
I wish I had gone to see the autumn leaves when you asked me to.
I wish I had spent more time talking to you.
I wish I had said these things more often.
Dad, you made delicious bread.
It was the most delicious bread in the world.
I shouldn't have washed it. I can't smell him anymore.
Dad. Dad.
Dad.
Dad, next time, be born as my child.
I'll take care of you.
I'll do everything that you did for me.
I'll pay back.
What should I do, dad?
Where is Kang Yoo Jung?
I haven't seen her for days.
Find her.
Yes.
No. Forget it.
You're no good at finding people.
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Wake up!
Wake up!
Here! Over here!
- She's dying. - Come this way.
This way.
Don't die.
Don't die without my permission.